Guide to the Records of the University Christian Foundation RG.39.3
New York University Archives
- Series 6: Programs
  - Student Strike, May 1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - SDS (Students for a Democratic Society), Feb 1968 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Triple Revolution Series, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Program Report, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - University Protestant Fellowship, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Urban Affairs Proposal, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Volunteer Research Project, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - World Hunger Coalition, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)